Go set up a new platform.
Thank you, sir.
Hello, sir.
Gu Ting.
I've been thinking about this a lot.
I think I need to tell you.
Otherwise,
I'd feel like I'm letting you down.
I'm sorry, sir.
I appreciate your feelings,
but I really can't return them.
Gu Ting,
you misunderstood.
I'm calling
about your father.
My dad?
Didn't you tell me before
that your father doesn't have a proper job?
Yeah.
Is there a problem with his job?
He is actually a fraudster.
Teacher Yan.
Even though my dad is unreliable,
he could never be a fraudster.
I wanted to talk to you properly,
but I never expected you to be like this.
I knew you wouldn't believe me.
I'll send you the documents.
See for yourself.
All this...
...was done by my dad.
A police friend of mine
mentioned your father, Gu Yan, in passing,
saying he's a fraudster on the run.
Don't worry.
I didn't report him.
But I have to tell you,
I can't bear to see him sent to prison.
Gu Ting.
My dad is getting old...
Let me handle this.
Come to the school now.
Let's have a proper talk
about how to help your father.
There's no need, sir.
I'll handle this myself.
Honey, you're back.
Look what Dad just bought you. Want it?
I...
This...
Dad bought this for you.
You could at least take a look.
I admit that recently,
well...
I haven't been there for you enough.
That's mainly because Dad
has been really busy with work lately.
Then let me ask you,
what exactly do you do for work?
Depends on when you mean.
Dad has done all kinds of jobs.
I do whatever makes money.
You scam people out there,
and come home to scam your own daughter?
How can you say that?
How could Dad ever lie to you?
Impossible.
Who sent this to you?
It doesn't matter who sent it.
I'm just asking if it's true.
It's fake.
I'm just doing business.
You're still trying to lie to me even now?
Fine.
It doesn't matter if you won't admit it.
Then starting today,
we will sever father-daughter ties.
Honey...
I'm begging you.
Just tell me straight up,
what do I need to do so you won't leave?
Turn yourself in.
No...
I mean...
I'm getting too old.
You're telling me to go to prison?
It's just...
I can't handle that kind of hardship.
I'm truly so disappointed in you.
Didn't you want to write a novel?
I bought you some reference books
and mystery collections.
I don't know if they'll be helpful.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
I swear I'll kill you today!
You bastard!
You damn old man!
What are you doing?!
What do you think I'm doing?!
I'll kill you!
You dare fight back?!
Seriously, what are you doing?!
What am I doing?!
You told my daughter my real identity!
Now she wants to sever father-daughter ties!
What am I doing?!
What the hell are you babbling about?
Since you called me last time
and told me to sever ties with Gu Ting,
I haven't contacted her again!
Impossible!
Who else knows my identity but you?!
No, I swear I'll kill you!
It's the truth!
What good does it do me to cross you now?
Then why drive a wedge between us?
To keep my daughter all to yourself!
Let me tell you,
I've got my own problems to worry about.
I'm getting close to the fraud ring boss.
Why would I complicate things?
What do you mean, your own problems?
My family
was killed by that man!
Who died in your family?
I can't tell you.
I'll tell you when I find out.
And also,
I really don't know how Gu Ting
found out your real identity.
But if you play with fire,
you're bound to get burned.
What do I do now?
This daughter of mine,
she's really going to leave me this time.
Alright.
Just go home and wait.
I'll help you figure something out.
By the way,
I'm sorry about just now.
Let me wipe that for you.
No need.
A bloody mess.
It doesn't look good.
Get away.
Just let me wipe it.
Get off me!
So annoying
Honey...
Just pick up the phone!
Why did you turn it off?
The number you dialed is powered off.
Please turn it on.
Honey...
You're worrying your dad to death.
I've looked everywhere.
I can't find her.
Wait, why are you here?
Around the school...
She's not where Gu Ting and I usually go.
Could something have happened to Tingting?
Think carefully.
Who else could tell Gu Ting your identity?
Well...
No one who knows me knows about Tingting.
And the people who know Tingting...
...couldn't possibly know my identity.
No, hold on.
I've helped you so many times.
You must help me this time, no matter what.
You don't have to tell me.
Gu Ting is a good girl.
I can't let anything happen to her.
If you know that, why not do something?
What good is it just standing around here?
Now what?
She's been kidnapped.
Wait.
How can you be sure she's been kidnapped?
This wasn't sent from a phone.
This is an Electronic signal.
I have a gift for you here.
I've located her.
Where?
But the signal is very weak.
Hold it higher.
Higher, higher, higher.
Come on, check it!
It's not my signal.
It's her signal.
If you hold it higher, won't she get it too?
Bro Liu.
Grass Snake.
They've got their eyes on you, right?
No.
The police are cracking down so hard now.
Where could they possibly hide?
Sun Ming, Gu Yan and I suspect...
Grass Snake likely kidnapped Gu Ting.
It should be where they usually punish people.
I'll send you the notes.
Okay, I got it.
Xiao Lin.
Track it and alert the SWAT team at once.
Move out right now!
Yes, sir!
Who's there?
Is anyone there?
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm...
Like I'd tell you that.
Help!
Is anybody out there?!
Scream! Louder!
Let's see if anyone comes to save you.
Louder!
Help!